Welcome to the Universal Translation demo.
In this video, we'll show you
how subtitle translation works.
First, upload your SRT file
to the translation platform.
Then select your source and target languages.
The AI will automatically detect terminology
that needs consistent translation.
You can review and edit
each subtitle individually.
Timestamps are preserved exactly
as they appear in the original file.
When you're done, export the translated
subtitles as a new SRT file.
The platform supports multiple languages
including Chinese, Japanese, and Korean.
Thank you for watching!
We hope you enjoy using Universal Translation.